<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Valid class styles:
'qigong'
'taiji'
'wushu'
'sanshou'
'xingyi'
'bagua'
'lhbf'
'xiaoyao'
-->
<schedule>
	<announcement>
		<title>Important Notice</title>
		<description>Due to the severity of the coronavirus situation, we request that students who have recently travelled by airplane, cruise or train refrain from coming to classes until after 14 days of quarantine.\n\nThis also applies to anyone who might have had close contact with people who might be affected by the virus as well as to students who have cold, flu, fever or cough.\n\nThank you for your cooperation and understanding!</description>
		<showUntilDate>2020-06-10</showUntilDate>
    	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Beginner Liu He Ba Fa (Water style) Sword class</title>
		<description>Liu He Ba Fa Sword is a sword form utilizes the techniques and skills of Liu He Ba Fa style. Liu He Ba Fa (Water Style) is one of the major internal style martial arts. It originally passed down from generation to generation only to a handful of gifted and chosen students with exemplary courage and moral character. Liu He Ba Fa literally means Six Harmonies and Eight Principles. It utilizes the power of Xingyi as its center, utilizes the stepping patterns of Bagua for its turning and spinning, and utilizes the neutralizing power of Taiji for its variations. Its movements are sometimes high, sometimes low, sometimes fast, sometimes slow. These movements resemble that of floating clouds, and flowing water that is sometimes calm, sometimes surging. Therefore, it is also known as Water Style.\n\nClass starts when 10 registrantion requirement is met, estimate to start on Jan 6th, 2020, Monday, 7-8pm </description>
		<moreLink>http://www.shouyuliang.com/classes-schedules-and-fees/liu-he-ba-fa-class.shtml</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2020-03-10</showUntilDate>
    	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Beginner Traditional Chen Style Old Frame No 1 Long Fist class</title>
		<description>Chen style Taiji is known for its silk reeling power and steady footwork. Old frame no 1 routine is also called Lau Jia Yi Lu Long Fist.\n\nClass starts when 10 registrantion requirement is met, estimate to start on April 4th, 2020, Sat, 3-4pm\nJan 7th, 2020, Tue, 6-7pm</description>>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2020-06-20</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>	 
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Beginner Traditional Chen Style Taiji Old Frame No 2 Cannon Fist</title>
		<description>Chen style Taiji is known for its silk reeling power and steady footwork. Old frame no 2 routine is also called Lau Jia Er Lu Cannon Fist.\n\nClass starts when 10 registrantion requirement is met, estimate to start on Feb 24th, 2020, Monday, 6-7pm</description>>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2020-04-28</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>  
        <announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Wuji Xiao Yao System Class</title>
		<description>One year has passed. This class is now available for registration again. This is a one-year training class. Training includes Dapeng Qigong, Body Conditioning, Xiao Yao Style form and Wuji Form Part 1.\n\nClass starts on Oct 15th, Tue 7-8:15pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/wuji-xiao-yao-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2019-11-30</showUntilDate>
	</announcement> 
	<announcement>
		<title>2019 SYL Annual Internal Martial Arts and Qigong Retreat is now available for registration!</title>
		<description>This year we offer Qigong, Wuji, Taiji,and Liu He Ba Fa (Water Style) classes from Aug 1st to Aug 7th. For more information, please click to view our workshop page.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/2019-internal-chinese-martial-arts-and-qigong-retreat.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2019-08-08</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Taiji for Beginner - 24 Form</title>
		<description>The 24 form Taiji is a standarized Taiji quan routine that was compiled by the Chinese Sports Committee in 1956. It is based on the Yang style Taijiquan, taking about six minutes to perform. It gives beginner an introduction to the essetial elements of Taijiquan, yet retain the traditional flavor of the traditional longer hand forms. It is a great foundation for beginners.\n\nClass starts on Sept 5th, 2019 if 10 registrantion requirement is met, Thursday, 6:30-7:30pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2019-010-15</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>SYL Annual Banquet</title>
		<description>It's another year. Party time again! Please join us for an evening of exciting performances, yummy food and other activities.\nLocation: Floata Seafood Restaurant 400-180 Keefer St, Vancouver\nDate and Time: January 26th. 6-10pm\nTickets are available on a first-come, first-served basis. For tickets, please email SYLwushu@gmail.com</description>>
		<showUntilDate>2019-01-26</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming 42 Taiji Sword - Beginner Sword class</title>
		<description>The 42 Taiji Sword is a standarized Taiji sword routine that was compiled in 1989. It is based on the Yang style Taijiquan, but also includes moves and components from the other major style such as Chen, Wu and Sun styles of Taijiquan. It is a popular form for personal health benefits as well as for competition\n\nClass starts on  April 30th, 2019, every Tuesday, 6-7pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2019-05-30</showUntilDate>
	</announcement> 
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Chen Style Taiji for Beginner - 56 Compulsory Routine class</title>
		<description>Chen style Taiji is known for its silk reeling power and steady footwork. Chen Style 56 is a compulsory routine which was compiled by Chinese Sport Committee based on the traditional Chen style No 1 and No 2 routine. .\n\nClass starts Oct 1st, 2018, Mon, 6-7pm</description>>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2018-11-15</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>	
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Liu He Ba Fa (Water Style) class</title>
		<description>Liu He Ba Fa (Water Style) is one of the major internal style martial arts. It originally passed down from generation to generation only to a handful of gifted and chosen students with exemplary courage and moral character. Liu He Ba Fa literally means Six Harmonies and Eight Principles. It utilizes the power of Xingyi as its center, utilizes the stepping patterns of Bagua for its turning and spinning, and utilizes the neutralizing power of Taiji for its variations. Its movements are sometimes high, sometimes low, sometimes fast, sometimes slow. These movements resemble that of floating clouds, and flowing water that is sometimes calm, sometimes surging. Therefore, it is also known as Water Style.\n\nClass starts on Feb 18th, Mon, 7-8pm </description>
		<moreLink>http://www.shouyuliang.com/classes-schedules-and-fees/liu-he-ba-fa-class.shtml</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2019-03-28</showUntilDate>
    	</announcement> 
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Traditional Yang Style Taiji- Beginner</title>
		<description>Yang style Taiji is one of the most popular and widely practised style in the world today. It's known for its soft and graceful movements. The form is practiced most often for its calming meditational and health benefit purpose.\n\nClass starts on Jan 05th, 2019, every Saturday 3-4pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2019-02-25</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Yang Style Taiji - Beginner class</title>
		<description>Yang style Taiji is one of the most popular and widely practised style in the world today. It's known for its soft and graceful movements. It's very sutiabe for beginners to start with.\nClass starts June 24th, 2017, every Saturday 3-4pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2017-08-30</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Taiji 42 Compulsory Routine class</title>
		<description>The 42 form Taiji is a standarized Taiji quan routine. It is based on the Yang style Taijiquan, but also includes moves and components from the other major style such as Chen, Wu and Sun styles of Taijiquan. \n\nClass starts on May 15th, 2018, Tuesday 6-7pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2018-06-20</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>	  
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Traditional Wushu Class</title>
		<description>In this class Grandmaster Liang will be teaching a series of traditional styles eg. Xingyi, Bagua, Emei Snake, White Ape Sword etc.\n\nClass starts on Jan 23rd, 2018, every Tue 5-6pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/wushu-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2018-02-30</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Chen Style Taiji Sword class</title>
		<description>Chen style Taiji is known for its silk reeling power and steady footwork. Sword is the most widely practiced weapon for Taiji. The movements in this routine are sometimes slow, sometimes fast, sometimes soft, sometimes hard, sometimes high and sometimes low. It is graceful and powerful.\n\nClass starts Aug 8th, 2017, Tue, 6-7pm</description>
		<moreLink>http://www.shouyuliang.com/classes-schedules-and-fees/taiji-class.shtml</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2017-09-15</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>2017 Internal Chinese Martial Arts and Qigong Retreat: August 1 - 7, 2017</title>
		<description>Registration for the 2017 Internal Chinese Martial Arts and Qigong Retreat is now open.  Classes this year include Wuji Xiao Yao System, Liu He Ba Fa Sword, Daoist Qigong and Chen Style Taiji.  All seminars are taught personally by Grandmaster Shou-Yu Liang, Master Helen Liang and Master Chenhan Yang.  Seminars are from August 1 - 7, 9AM - 12PM, 2PM - 5PM.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/2017-internal-chinese-martial-arts-and-qigong-retreat.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2017-08-07</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>Qigong and Taiji seminar with Master Helen Liang and Master Chenhan Yang</title>
		<description>Friday October 6 - Sunday the 8th.
			Mt. Lebanon Recreation Center, 900 Cedar Blvd., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 15228\n\n
			Join Masters Liang and Yang as they co-teach Qigong and Taiji forms from the best selling YMAA DVDs—Qigong For Women, Qigong for Cancer, and The 24 Movement Simplified Taiji Form—as part of One Pine Institute’s “Living Masters Series”.
			\n\nThe workshops will be held Friday evening (7-9), Saturday morning and afternoon (9-11:30 and 1:30-4:00), and Sunday morning (9-12). Cost for the workshops is $60 for Friday evening, and $70 for each of the Saturday and Sunday sessions. Registration prior to September 29th is discounted $10 per session.
			\n\nTo register on-line, visit www.ONEPINE.ORG
			All of the workshops will be held in the Mt. Lebanon neighborhood of Pittsburgh, repeatedly voted one of the best places in live in the United States. Close by are a wide variety of restaurants and shops.
			\n\nFor more information contact Dr. David Clippinger 412-480-9177 or info@onepine.org.
		</description>
		<moreLink>http://www.onepine.org</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2017-10-09</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>	
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming 32 Taiji Sword - Beginner Sword class</title>
		<description>The 32 Taiji Sword is a standarized Taiji sword routine that was compiled by the Chinese Sports Committee in 1957. It is based on the traditional Yang style Taiji Sword routine. It gives beginner an introduction to the essetial elements of Taiji sword, yet retain the traditional flavor of the traditional Yang style Taiji sword form. It is a great foundation for beginners.\n\nClass starts on April 21st, 2018, every Saturday, 3-4pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2018-06-15</showUntilDate>
	</announcement> 
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Chen Style Taiji Sword class</title>
		<description>Chen style Taiji is known for its silk reeling power and steady footwork. Sword is the most widely practiced weapon for Taiji. The movements in this routine are sometimes slow, sometimes fast, sometimes soft, sometimes hard, sometimes high and sometimes low. It is graceful and powerful.\n\nClass starts May 25th, 2017, Thur, 7-8pm</description>
		<moreLink>http://www.shouyuliang.com/classes-schedules-and-fees/taiji-class.shtml</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2017-07-05</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	<announcement>
		<title>New Simplified Tai Chi For Beginner 24 form DVD by Master Helen Liang is now available!</title>
		<description>In this DVD Master Helen Liang is not only giving beautiful demonstration of the form, she also presents thorough teaching on the basics of Taichi, movement details and applications.  Simplified Tai Chi 24 for Beginners DVD is the perfect way to experience the amazing health benefits of a shortened tai chi form, no matter your current fitness level.</description>>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/dvd/simplified-taiji-for-beginners.php</moreLink>	
	<showUntilDate>2016-02-30</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>			
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Wudang Dan Jian Elixir Sword class</title>
		<description>Wudang Sword plays an important role in traditional Chinese Wushu. The form movements are graceful and smooth. The goal is to achieve the unification of the sword and the body.\n\nClass starts on Dec 1st, 2015, Tue, 6-7pm</description>>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2016-01-25</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>   
	<announcement>
		<title>2016 SYL Annual Internal Martial Arts and Qigong Retreat is now available for registration!</title>
		<description>This year we offer Qigong, Wuji and Beginner Taiji classes from Aug 1st to Aug 7th. For more detail information please click to view our workshop page.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/2016-internal-chinese-martial-arts-and-qigong-retreat.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2016-08-08</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>  
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Wudang Taiji Sword class</title>
		<description>Wudang is the one of the major school in China. It plays an important role in traditional Chinese Wushu. This form bears Taiji sword and Wudang Sword basics and flavours.\n\nClass starts Sept 27th, 2016, Tue, 6-7pm</description>
		<moreLink>http://www.shouyuliang.com/classes-schedules-and-fees/taiji-class.shtml</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2016-11-15</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>   
	<announcement>
		<title>Traditional Yang Style Taiji Sword</title>
		<description>Class starts on Feb 10th, 2015, every Tue 6-7pm.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/taiji-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2015-03-15</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>  
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming Beginner Liu He Ba Fa (Water Style) class - San Pan Shi Er Shi</title>
		<description>The San Pan Shi Er Shi is a 12 animal routine for Water Style. It is also a foundation training routine that includes advancing, retreating, rising and lowering movements which is designed to develop reaction skills for combat.\n\nClass starts Dec 10th, 2016, Sat, 3-4pm</description>
		<moreLink>http://www.shouyuliang.com/classes-schedules-and-fees/liu-he-ba-fa-class.shtml</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2017-01-20</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>	    
	<announcement>
		<title>Upcoming New Qigong Class</title>
		<description>Qigong most often refers to the art and science of using breath, posture, movement, and/or sound to cleanse, refine, accumulate and circulate Qi in the body.Through the cultivation and regulation of body, mind, breathing, and vocalization, our resistance to disease, adaptability to the external environment, and immunity to pathogenic influences is strengthened. With a strong immune system, diseases are prevented, creating a state of super health, vitality, and youthfulness for the practitioner.\nQigong class will be covering varies types of Qigong such us Health Maintenance, Daoist and Buddhist Qigong\n\nSat Health Qigong class starts on Jan 25th 2020, Sat, 2-3pm\n\nThur Beginner One-Year Daoist Qigong minimum 30 registration to start, 5:30-6:30pm\n\nFri Advance One-Year Daoist Qigong starts on March 1st, 2019, if minimum 20 registration requirment is met Fri 5:30-6:30pm\n\nFriday Daoist Qigong is a ONE-YEAR Daoist Qigong class starts when minimum number of registrants of 30 is met. The Daoist Qigong Cultivation Class mainly revolves around the Cultivation of Traditional Internal Elixir（内丹) and the Double Cultivation of Body and Spirit （性命双修）.The class begins with an introduction of several breathing techniques with a goal of building and strengthening Qi in the Dantian and to prepare one for Cosmic Circulation（周天循环 ). Then it moves to the Cultivation of Spirit (性功修炼）which includes methods such as “Golden Light”, “Gathering Light”, “Big Dipper”, “Initiating the Spirit”, “Gather Together the Five Elements”（攒簇五行）、“Harmonizing Four Phases”（合和四象） “Regulating the Spirit Light”, “Nurturing the Original Spirit”, “Letting Out the Original Spirit”, “Returning of the Original Spirit”, etc. “Cultivation of the Physical Body” that will be introduced in class including methods such as “Reflect Back of the Spirit on Dantian”, “Embryonic Breathing”, “Gathering Herbs (obtains internal essence)”, etc. These are methods that aim to train oneself moving out of the form and into the formless（出有入無). The for mentioned methods are merely a small part of of the essence of “Daoist Qigong Cultivation” which has had a history of thousands of years, and they serve to help one obtain Pre-Heaven Essence, strengthen the body, maintain health, regain youth and ultimately build a strong foundation for yet higher level cultivations.</description>
		<moreLink>http://shouyuliang.com/classes/qigong-class.php</moreLink>
		<showUntilDate>2030-12-31</showUntilDate>
	</announcement>
	
	<class style="qigong">
		<title>Health Qigong</title>
		<startDate>2020-01-25</startDate>
		<day>Saturday</day>
		<startTime>14:00</startTime>
		<endTime>15:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 10 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>315</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>4</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="qigong">
		<title>Beginner Daoist Qigong One Year Program</title>
		<startDate>2019-02-28</startDate>
		<day>Thursday</day>
		<startTime>17:00</startTime>
		<endTime>18:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 30 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class. This is a ONE-YEAR long course. Payment of $1260 in full will be collected prior to the start of the first class. Fee will be $1380 if registering after class has started for a month.</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>40</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>1260</cost>
	      <frequency>YEAR</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="qigong">
		<title>Advance Daoist Qigong One Year Program</title>
		<startDate>2019-03-01</startDate>
		<day>Friday</day>
		<startTime>17:30</startTime>
		<endTime>18:30</endTime>
		<note>Min 30 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class. This is a ONE-YEAR long course. Payment of $1260 in full will be collected prior to the start of the first class. Fee will be $1380 if registering after class has started for a month.</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>40</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>1260</cost>
	      <frequency>YEAR</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="Taiji">
		<title>Beginner Traditional Chen Style Taiji Old Frame No 2 Cannon Fist</title>
		<startDate>2020-02-24</startDate>
		<day>Monday</day>
		<startTime>18:00</startTime>
		<endTime>19:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 10 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class. Estimated duration would be eight months. 1st payment of $315 will be collected at the first class and 2nd payment of $315 will be collected at the beginning of the 5th month.</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>315</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>4</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="Taiji">
		<title>Beginner Chen Style Old Frame No 1 Long Fist class</title>
		<startDate>2020-04-04</startDate>
		<day>Saturday</day>
		<startTime>15:00</startTime>
		<endTime>16:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 10 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class. Estimated duration would be 12 months. 1st payment of $315 will be collected at the first class, 2nd payment of $315 will be collected at the beginning of the 5th month, and 3rd payment of $315 will be collected at the beginning of the 9th month.</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>315</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>4</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>	
	<class style="Taiji">
		<title>Beginner Chen Style Old Frame No 1 Long Fist class</title>
		<startDate>2020-01-07</startDate>
		<day>Tuesday</day>
		<startTime>18:00</startTime>
		<endTime>19:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 10 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class. Estimated duration would be 12 months. 1st payment of $315 will be collected at the first class, 2nd payment of $315 will be collected at the beginning of the 5th month, and 3rd payment of $315 will be collected at the beginning of the 9th month.</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>315</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>4</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>	
	<class style="Taiji">
		<title>Taiji 42 sword -Beginner Class</title>
		<startDate>2019-04-02</startDate>
		<day>Tuesday</day>
		<startTime>18:00</startTime>
		<endTime>19:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 10 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class. This is an eight months class. 1st payment of $315 will be collected at the first class and 2nd payment of $315 will be collected at the beginning of the 5th month.</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>315</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>4</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="lhbf">
		<title>Beginner Beginner Liu He Ba Fa (Water style) Sword class</title>
		<startDate>2020-01-06</startDate>
		<day>Monday</day>
		<startTime>19:00</startTime>
		<endTime>20:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 10 people to start. Please register early to avoid cancellation of the class. Estimated duration would be eight months. 1st payment of $315 will be collected at the first class and 2nd payment of $315 will be collected at the beginning of the 5th month.</note>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>315</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>4</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>			
	<class style="wushu">
		<title>Wushu and Sanshou Training</title>
		<startDate>Ongoing</startDate>
		<day>Friday</day>
		<startTime>19:00</startTime>
		<endTime>21:00</endTime>
		<note></note>
		<fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>100</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote>For attending EITHER/BOTH Friday and Saturday classes. Payment to be made at the beginning of each month.</feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="wushu">
		<title>Wushu and Sanshou Training</title>
		<startDate>Ongoing</startDate>
		<day>Saturday</day>
		<startTime>16:00</startTime>
		<endTime>18:00</endTime>
		<note></note>
		<fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	   <fee>
	      <cost>100</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote>For attending EITHER/BOTH Friday and Saturday classes. Payment to be made at the beginning of the each month.</feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="wushu">
		<title>Traditional Wushu</title>
		<startDate>2018-01-23</startDate>
		<day>Tuesday</day>
		<startTime>17:00</startTime>
		<endTime>18:00</endTime>
		<note>Min 10 registrants to start the class</note>
		<fee>
	      <cost>30</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	    </fee>
	    <fee>
	      <cost>315</cost>
	      <frequency>MONTH</frequency>
	      <duration>Every 4</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>
	<class style="xiaoyao">
		<title>Wuji Xiao Yao System and Dapeng Qigong</title>
		<startDate>2019-10-15</startDate>
		<day>Tuesday</day>
		<startTime>19:00</startTime>
		<endTime>20:15</endTime>
		<note>As training in this style is long-term, payment for one year in full.</note>
		<fee>
	      <cost>40</cost>
	      <frequency>CLASS</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	    </fee>
	    <fee>
	      <cost>1140</cost>
	      <frequency>YEAR</frequency>
	      <duration>1</duration>
	      <numberOfFreeClasses></numberOfFreeClasses>
	      <feeNote></feeNote>
	   </fee>
	</class>

</schedule>